It's been a long time.
It's been a long time since I've been involved with Ebichu, and that's how I'm spinning it,
I've been going to live shows and it's all right,
It's been the same since I started working again,
I'm so happy to see the camera rolling like this.
I'm so happy!
No, I'm happy too. I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
Suddenly, now, suddenly, it's getting crowded!
Hey! What's up?
You've been talking all this time.
That's right.
Because, um, Kimoto-san's
Since we met...
I've just been on TV.
I've been allowed to appear on TV too lately.
During that time, when we talked about Mr. Kimoto
It was all cut.
Really? What are you doing?
I'm so happy! Thank you so much!
But Hina-chan is on the Oni Ren-chan.
She was messing around with Kamaitachi and the others.
We also got it... that she was messing around with them.
Yes, that's right.
And she turned red.
Speaking of the two of them, the sauna...
He's our mentor, he's our teacher.
And then he passed it on to Maya, who passed it on to me
Yes...
But back then...
Hina-chan was the one who was most interested in it, right?
That's right.
I was like, “Wow, that's great,” and then Hina-chan didn't go for it at all.
I don't think she ever did.
Not even once?
Maybe.
I asked her out a few times, but she said not today.
What's your cue?
From the way she was acting, it looked like she was into it.
Another thing I'm interested in is you, Cocona.
I still feel like a father in the review process.
Cocona is getting a little too flashy lately.
Pappa's getting a little too flashy lately
Pappa's skin is a mess.
I'm worried that she's getting a little too flashy.
Is she okay? Is she selling vegetables?
I don't think she selling vegetables.
Really?
Maybe it's just looks.
I see.
Recently, you know, backstage we were talking too much about “gyaru-gyaru” (gal"),
And then suddenly, she said that she wasn't “gyaru” and got mad, mad, mad.
She's so cute.
She's really cute.
I don't think she is a gyaru.
She looks like she's a returnee from America.
Sure, she's cute, but I wonder if she'll be okay.
Yes, if anything happens. Let me call her personally.
No. So, to consult.
I'll call Mayama and Yasumoto when I need to talk to her about something,
I've never done that with Cocona-chan,
I really thought I was being a little too flashy once.
You really are a father, aren't you?
That's right. I felt a little like a father,
I held back from contacting her.
Yes.
Cocona might be in her rebellious phase right now,
She seems to be angry with Dad.
It stinks!
So much so that I don't even want to be with her.
You stink! Like.
Don't wash it in the washing machine for the rest of your life.
It's really thin.
This is the 15th anniversary of Ebichu, right?
Yes, it is.
Fifteenth anniversary.
Yes.
Yeah.
Fifteenth anniversary.
In the blink of an eye.
How long have you been doing Ebichu Nanyanen?
We've been doing radio for...
Ten?
How long have you been doing it?
About 11 years.
Over 10 years.
That's been going on for a long time, too.
It really has.
That's what it is now, isn't it?
Oswald and Nakanishi Nasu.
I'm getting to know Nasu-Nakanishi pretty well.
How's it going? How's Nasunakanishi? - Oh, really? They're more... how do you say? They're more like a grandpa rather than dad? A grand-patterned feeling.
It's like everyone is looking out for me. They are smiling at me.
The Kamai-tachi are already on TV. I'm sure they'll be there.
How are the Kamaitachi?
I wonder if they remember us, we've feel lonely because we've become a little distant.
Of course they remember you.
They've getting so much popular that I'm a little bit worried.
Right now, you know.
But I'm sure you're watching X and so on.
I mean, they do reposts every once in a while.
The Kamaitachi. I don't know about recently.
I don't know about these days, but I don't see them much anymore.
What? It's become less and less?
I'm just saying, to put it bluntly, to put it bluntly.
Lately, I don't see them.
Yamauchi, I saw him reposting quite a lot.
Do you have that image?
Yes, recently.
What's going on these days?
Maybe because He's busy.
You're busy? How do you like it?
You might see this all the time.
Kamaitachi, repost.
Please repost.
Quote repost if you can.
The one you're responding to.
This is my office.
It's my first time here.
It's so beautiful.
Yeah, we use this as a lyric studio.
It's also used as a lyric studio, and we have an office in the back.
When we have another event...
I'm in business now, but it's also my office, so when you have an event...
I'm running it as an office.
I'm in business now.
If you ever have any events, please do!
That's great.
I'd love to.
I'm so proud of you for getting it in there so quickly.
I'm sure you'll have fan-beating and stuff.
And I'll give you the fee later.
Okay, okay.
Wait a minute. Sometimes they cut it down a notch or two, but just wait.
I'll wait.
You never know, they might make us buy a jar.
They might come out with a jar. A jar.
This one.
I wonder what it is.
Sauna hat.
Oh, my God! Yay!
Thank you!
Is it original?
Yes.
Wow!
That's great.
May I open it?
I talked to Mayama about this.
I remember.
I remember... I remember... which logo do you think is cuter?
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, so that's what happened.
We talked about which one was cuter.
Oh, this barcode is so cute!
It's so cute!
When I was struggling with some of these things...
I consult with Mayama.
and say, “Mayama, would you like this one?
I'm sorry, I'm just talking.
Super cute, cute, thick, and really curly.
Hey...
Hey, when you move it after that...
It's easy to dry, it's cute like this, yay!
So practical... they dry very slowly, don't they?
It's true that the middle rope is hard to dry.
And one more Mayama,
I think Mayama once,
You were interviewed in a sauna magazine or something.
Yes, I was interviewed.
When I saw that, I was amazed.
I was like, “Wow, you've come this far“,
She said that Kimoto-san taught him how to do it.
I read the text and it didn't come out at all.
Kimoto-san was treated like Voldemort at that time.
It's not so easy with the name.
I know, I know.
I wanted to mention master's name right away.
I understand. I understand that.
No, no, no, no, so please take this.
By all means, we will use it from now on.
From us, too, the live...
There it is!
Last year? Last year.
Earlier this year.
The leader of the show we did at the beginning of this year.
Thanks a lot.
So, do you have a goodbye secret base?
Oh! I think it's in there.
I think it's in there.
You're not in it!
I don't think it's in there.
Goodbye secret base.
No, you know what?
I can jump through all the hoops.
Goodbye, secret base.
I'm glad, I'm glad, I'm glad.
I want you to see the knife work
It's a different kind of soundtrack.
I'll make it for fun
Great, I like it too
It's the last one.
Last but not least.
That's good.
Thank you very much.
I'm a little bit emotional... that we haven't done this in a while.
It's been a while since we've been together.
I'm happy, happy, happy.
I'll do my best to get involved again.
I'll try my best to be more involved in different areas.
I'll do my best too.
So please don't forget about me
Don't forget about me.
Please don't forget about me.
Even me, Mr. Teacher.
Also, since this is the Ebichu family watching us.
I just want to say that I really want to thank all the Ebichu family fans
I'd like to say that I'm really grateful to all the Ebichu family fans who encouraged me through DMs when I was in turmoil...
Well, thank you very much.
Thank you so much for all the DMs and encouragement.
And if I had any announcements or live show announcements or tour announcements or anything like that.
And when I posted announcements about shows and tours and stuff, you'd repost them and stuff like that.
Yes, that's right.
So, I'm touring in 47 prefectures in Japan, and I'm going to be in many places.
I'm touring in 47 prefectures in Japan, and at various places
They came to my live shows saying they were Emichu's family.
You also sold tickets by hand, didn't you?
We sold our music at about 30 places all over the country.
Yes, so I was thinking, “There are fans of Ebichu all over the country,
We really had all of those families come to see us.
Well, we are going to tour again next year.
If you came last year, please bring one or two people with you.
Please bring one or two people with you.
That's a lot of people.
Take two people with you.
Not just one.
Two each.
Three at a time.
Like this, like this.
We're looking forward to working with you.
Thank you very much, and we would like to ask you to do us a favor. Thank you very much.
We have a favor to ask you...
TikTok!
Are you on TikTok?
We have been using TikTok for our live performances, but we haven't really started to use it yet.
We are currently working on a project called “Mikachu Project.
We have a project called “Unidentified Junior High School Student X” and we want it to go viral.
We want it to go viral, and we want people to know about it, so we're asking everyone to dance.
We'd like you to dance with us. I see.
Dancing? Dance.
Dancing?
Can you do it?
Yes, I can.
Then, what do you mean?
I can't do it at all.
I don't know...
I don't know what to say.
I'll just do it the way it's supposed to be done.
I'll learn how to do it.
It's really easy
It's so easy, but it's so hard to get it off my chest.
Right hand? Yes, right hand.
Zukkun zukkun, it's coming to my chest.
Tell me the name of this feeling.
Tell me. Let's see.
Zukkunzukki-kun, it's coming to my chest.
Tell me the name of this feeling
Se-no.
Zukkyu zukkyu, it's in my chest
Tell me the name of this feeling
OK, it's done!
Can you do it already?
Can you do it?
This is fast.
Now repeat this all the way through, like, four times.
Do it four times.
Repeat four times.
How fast?
I'm going to do an unidentified junior high school student, and it's called X.
After you've done it four times, after you've done this...
I'm going to make an X.
Tell me the name of this feeling that keeps on dokundokun dokundokun dokundokun, the acceleration of the speed without time.
Forget about my breasts, let's just dance for now
Dokun, dokun, dokun...
Wow, he's so fast! He swallowed it so fast!
Let's not forget... this is here... or this is here... Wow! That's great! He swallowed it so fast!
Let's not forget.
I mean, can't you hurry up and tell me I'm wearing this?
Oh! I told you!
I saw it when I came to the office.
I saw you in it when I came to the office.
It's so familiar.
I'm so familiar with it, I can't stop the throbbing in my heart. Tell me the name of this feeling... the throbbing that keeps on happening.
So, is that it? Are you saying goodbye?
Yes, thank you very much.
I'll take you out to dinner next time.
Thank you!
Please do.
I'll go to dinner with you.
You can pass it around when we eat.
What? You're so quick to turn it into a job, Ms. Kimoto.
I don't think of it as work.
A hobby.
I just want to get out.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much and please subscribe to our channel.